<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Jiajie Li</title>
    <link>https://jiajie.media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Jiajie Li</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 15:07:22 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jiajie.media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Identifying human interactions in built environment: deep learning analytics on camera data for urban vibrancy evaluation</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/cross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 15:07:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/cross/</guid>
      <description>Cross-City Transfer Learning for Anti-epidemic Policies and Traffic Flow Prediction   Abstract In recent years, with the maturity of sensing technology and computing environment, various kinds of big data have been quietly born in cities, such as traffic flow, weather data, road networks, points of interest, mobile trajectories and social media. However, the imbalance of urban development level and the heterogeneity of urban data make it extremely challenging to generalize urban computing on a large scale, and most of the existing urban knowledge migration work focuses on one specific task, modeling and optimizing for specific datasets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identifying human interactions in built environment: deep learning analytics on camera data for urban vibrancy evaluation</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/vibrancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 15:07:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/vibrancy/</guid>
      <description>Identifying human interactions in built environment: deep learning analytics on camera data for urban vibrancy evaluation   Abstract Spatial revitalization has been widely regarded as the main goal for urban design. The increasing availability of multi-source data in recent years enables researchers to create better metrics to evaluate vibrancy. Despite the consensus that the count of people flow works as a significant indicator, it is incomplete for loosing information about activities in which people are involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identifying human interactions in built environment: deep learning analytics on camera data for urban vibrancy evaluation</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 15:07:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/wifi/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Detailed Spatial Temporal Activities and Urban Vibrancy via Wi-Fi Big Data: Case of LivingLine Shanghai as an Urban Prototype   Abstract Urban vibrancy is a topic of great concern in the field of urban design and planning. However, the definition and measurement of urban vibrancy have not been consistently and clearly followed. With the development of technologies such as big data and machine learning, urban researchers have been able to adopt some new methods that break the tradition to quantitatively evaluate urban vibrancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parasite-Host Network for Video Crowd Counting</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/phnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 15:07:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/phnet/</guid>
      <description>Parasite-Host Network for Video Crowd Counting   Demo Video, Github
Abstract Crowd counting plays an increasingly important role in public security. Recently, many crowd counting methods for a single image have been proposed but few studies have focused on using temporal information from image sequences of videos to improve prediction performance. In the existing methods using videos for crowd estimation, temporal features and spatial features are modeled jointly for the prediction, which makes the model less efficient in extracting spatiotemporal features and difficult to improve the performance of predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supporting Therapeutic Storytelling and Therapist’s Neutrality in Sandtray Therapy Through a Digital Twin</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 15:07:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/therapy/</guid>
      <description>Supporting Therapeutic Storytelling and Therapist’s Neutrality in Sandtray Therapy Through a Digital Twin   Abstract Sandtray therapy is a form of expressive therapy. Taking the form of a digital twin system, we present a novel tool to support sandtray therapy, designed to inspire the client’s self-expression and use quantitative data to supervise therapists to become more neutral. As figurines are placed by clients, the screen displays a living virtual world synchronously using computer vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equity WITHOUT Zoning</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/ewz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:40:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/portfolio/ewz/</guid>
      <description>Equity WITHOUT Zoning   Link to the online version: http://ewz.media.mit.edu/
Link to the docker repository: https://hub.docker.com/r/jajamoa/css2020
Featured Video   Workshop Record    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  My name is Jiajie Li (李嘉杰), and I also go by Chance. I am a senior undergrad at School of Software Engineering, Tongji University, where I am fortunate to be jointly advised by Shengjie Zhao and Hongming Zhu. I am also pleased to have worked with Yan Zhang and Can Wang during my undergraduate years.
I am currently a visiting student at the City Science (formerly Changing Places) group at the MIT Media Lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jiajie.media/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiajie.media/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email  jiajie [at] mit [dot] edu jiajie_li [at] alumni [dot] tongji [dot] edu [dot] cn   Social  Github LinkedIn  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
